

bonniesbrightideas@gmail.com
714.392.5346
https://bonniesbrightideas.github.io/
https://www.linkedin.com/in/bonniesbrightideas/

### **SUMMARY**

User-centered Designer with a thoughtful and creative approach to problem solving by combining usability viewpoints to design web and mobile applications with impact. Thrives on creating compelling designs to enhance user experiences to grow brand loyalty, create user delight, and make memorable experiences.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **ELI HOME** UX/UI Designer | Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

Contracted project to redesign clients' outdated website, worked with stakeholders to conduct needfinding, applied qualitative and quantitative user research to explore user needs, card sorted, lead the design vision, sketched, wireframed, tested, prototyped, and implemented.

#### **PROJECTS**

### Virtual Education Website Redesigned | Oct 2020

Redesigned West Hollywood Elementary School's website to enhance virtual learning with UX Research, UI Design, & Frontend Development.

#### **Government** Website Redesigned | July 2020

Redesigned the U.S. Department of Homeland Security's Website with UX Research & UI Design to streamline user flows and simplify navigation to improve public perception.

#### Recycling Mobile App | June 2020

Creation of a social recycling mobile app with UX Research & UI Design to excite and promote conservation and environmental awareness.

#### OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

## **COLLIERS** Property Administrator | May 2021 – Dec 2021

Managed and monitored conditions of 14 commercial properties across Southern California.

- Selected, wrote contracts, and provided access instructions for vendors for various property projects in maintaining and enhancing property conditions
- Managed tenant leases, issues, statements, and delinquencies.

**UTAH TRANSIT AUTHORITY** Property Administrator II | May 2015 – Oct 2019

Preserved and protected transit real estate assets covering 2,400 acres and servicing 1,400 sq. miles.

- Coordinated real estate development projects with government agencies and private developers by reviewing engineering plans, setting requirements, and managing contracts.
- Enhanced client relations by finding alternative solutions overcoming obstacles by maintaining project goals with open communication.

**CORESTRATEGY CORPORATION** Executive Assistant/Marketing Associate | Jun 2014 – April 2015

Maintained existing Fortune 1000 corporate client relations with strategic facility planning, facility acquisition, sublease lease renewals and renegotiation.

 Managed calendar, handled travel reservations, filed expense reports, composed correspondence; in addition to, updating company website and preparing marketing materials.

#### **EDUCATION**

**UX/UI CERTIFICATE** University of California, Irvine | October 2020 **B.S., BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION** University of California, Riverside | June 2008

# **SKILLS**

**TOOLS** XD, Figma, Sketch, InVision, Photoshop, Lightroom, Illustrator, Visual Studio Code

**RESEARCH** Data Analysis, User Persona, Usability Test, Storyboard, Guerilla Test, A/B Test, Interview, Survey, Comparative Analysis, User Insight, Empathy Map **PROTOTYPING** Site Map, Card Sorting, User flow, Wireframe, HTML, CSS, Java Script, Bootstrap, & Github